（忆往昔）
你终于有了一个家
You finally had a family.
建立了一个美满家庭
And you were building something.
我从没见过猎魔人能拥有如此幸福的生活
And it's as close to happiness as I've ever seen a hunter get.
迪恩
Dean?
- 本 待在那 - 我听到你
- Ben, just stay there. - I thought I heard you …
我让你别过来
I said stay back!
本连提都不想提
Ben won't even talk about it.
现在真的不是谈话的时候
This is the worst time in the universe to talk.
我们能以后再谈吗
Can we do this later?
迪恩 你推了我的孩子
You shoved my kid, Dean.
我们现在就得谈
How about we do this now?
但你和本…
But you and Ben…
我和本不能跟你淌这滩浑水
Me and Ben can't be in this with you.
路西法的牢笼
Lucifer's cage.
萨姆的灵魂被困在里面了
Sam's soul is stuck in that box.
那些记忆可谓十分不愉快
Nasty, those memories.
你不会想知道那些记忆会如何影响他
You don't want to know what they'll do to him.
- 不要这样做 - 别碰这个屏障
- Don't do this. - Don't scratch the wall.
死亡骑士并不只是
Death didn't just.
把你灵魂放回来 懂吗
shove your soul back in, okay?
他在你和你遗忘的那些事中间
He put up the great wall of Sam.
建立起了一道「萨姆之墙」
between you and the things that you don't remember.
你最好是相信我
And trust me when I say.
你不记得的那些事能杀死你
that the things you don't know could kill you.
小萨姆
Sammy?
Sammy?!
小萨姆 回答我
Sammy, talk to me!
（如今）
萨姆
Sam?
Sam.
萨姆
S-sam?
别这样
Oh, come on.
小萨姆
Sammy!
醒醒 醒醒
Come on, come on.
醒醒 该死
Come on, damn it.
喂 清醒了吗
Hey, hey, hey, you with me?
好
Okay.
快点 我带你离开这里
Come on. Come on, got to get you out of here.
（大瀑布专科学校 帕特森 新泽西州）
怎么…
What the…
是谁
Who's there?!
[邪恶力量 第6季第14集]
感觉如何
How you feel?
感觉像被颗行星给撞了
Like I got hit by a…Planet.
你很幸运 我是一名医生
Well, lucky for you, I'm a doctor.
给你买了咖啡 吃的 还有…
I got joe, grub, and…
这些是什么
What are they?
很有效
Effective.
我很好 谢谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
随你便
Suit yourself.
我昏迷了多久
So, how long was I out, again?
跟你说 大概两三分钟
I'm telling you, like two or three minutes.
怎么 你感觉是多久
Why, what'd it feel like to you?
大概有一周那么久
About a week, give or take.
你想聊聊那个吗
You want to talk about it?
「那个」
"It"?
是 不管那个是什么
Yeah, whatever that was.
那时你就像触电致死了一样
I mean, it was like you were freakin' electrocuted.
听着 那一点也不好玩
Look I mean, it wasn't fun,
但 我 我没事
But I-I'm…Fine.
好吧
Fine.
是地狱 对吧
It was hell, wasn't it?
你一脸的地狱相
You got a big, fat faceful of hell.
你有没有想过你可能会死
Ever cross your mind that you could've died?
- 拜托 - 我说真的
- Oh, come on. - I'm serious.
这可远不止什么「只是皮外伤」
And none of this "It's just a flesh wound" crap.
我们照你的方法做了
Cause we did it your way.
我们让你去探索记忆
We let you go explore,
而且所有我说过的糟糕的事也都发生了
and every bad thing that I said would happen happened.
你猜怎么着
So guess what …
过去的就让它过去
Past stays past.
我们不能再碰那屏障
We're not kicking that wall again.
那我只能无视它了吗
So I'm supposed to just ignore it?
是的
Yes.
迪恩…
Dean…
谁知道我过去…
I might've done…
都干了什么事
who knows what,
你却要我就这么忘掉它
and you want me to just forget about it?
你把那些回忆压制下去 然后通过
You shove it down, and you let it come out.
暴力和酗酒来发泄
in spurts of violence and alcoholism.
听起来挺健康
That sounds healthy.
对我挺有用
Well, works for me.
我没跟你开完笑
It's not a joke.
你命悬一线了 萨姆
Your life is on the line here, Sam.
没什么好争辩的了
This is not a debate.
当初你是一个没有灵魂的蠢蛋
I mean, first you were a-a soulless dickbag,
但你现在不是了
And now you're not.
咱说清楚没
So we good?
嗯 当然
Yeah. Sure.
那就好
Good.
那我们转移一下你的注意力好吗
Well, let's get your mind off it, shall we?
准备开工吗
You, uh, up for a job?
你发现什么了
Well, what do you got?
看门人昨晚于大学实验室被杀
Janitor murdered in a college lab last night.
门都是锁好的 楼里也没人进出
Doors were locked, nobody else in or out of the building.
棒极了 在哪
Great. Where to?
新泽西州的帕特森
Paterson, New Jersey.
也许在那能碰到史努基（美国电视名人）
Hey, maybe we'll have a Snooki sighting.
史努基是什么
What's a Snooki?
问得好
That is a good question.
快来看 这东西可真棒
Check it out. This thing's friggin' awesome!
做我的情人吧
Be my valentine.
哥啊 我们这是在工作 把它放回去
Dude, we're working. Put it back.
- 我把心掏给你 - 迪恩
- Have a heart. - Dean!
真扫兴
Buzz kill.
你闻到硫磺味了吗
You smell sulfur?
是的 我们在一个实验室里
Yeah, we're in a science lab.
好吧
Right.
谁打来的
Who is it?
是莉莎吧
So, Lisa?
管好你自己的事儿
Maybe you should mind your own business.
迪恩 跟她说说话能要你命啊
What's wrong with just talking to her, Dean?
多谢 知心姐姐
Thanks, Dr. Laura. That's …
见解十分深刻
that's very insightful.
你看看 时间到了
Look at that … our time's up.
鬼魂也疯狂
Ghosts gone wild.
有什么鬼怪在这儿
Something's up in here.
问题是 是什么
Question is, what?
好消息 萨姆
Sam, good news.
老大哥在监视着
Big brother's watching.
从拖把老兄的女友那查到了什么
So, what'd you find out from the, uh, mop jockey's girlfriend?
什么都没有
Nothing.
只知道他是个好人 去做礼拜
Just how great he was … went to church,
做慈善 看欢乐合唱团时给她按摩脚
donated to charity, rubbed her feet during "Glee."
我差点吐出来
I just threw up in my mouth.
不管怎样 我查了他的记录 很干净
Sorry. Anyway, I checked his record … spotless.
那栋科学大楼呢 有什么发现
What about the science building? Anything?
05年建成 那块地方也很正常
Built in '05. Nothing weird about the land.
在此之前 最大的灾难就是某个天才
Before this, the biggest mishap was some genius.
不小心将硫酸撒到了他的胯下
accidentally spilled sulfuric acid on his crotch.
他们都没有正经解剖过啥东西
They don't even dissect anything good in there.
比青蛙大点的东西 他们用就Ipad
Anything bigger than Kermit, they use an Ipad.
所以我们一无所获
So we got nothing?
是啊 屁都不知道
Yeah, a big steaming pile of it.
有人吗
Hello?
是谁
Who's there?!
强尼
Jonny?!
是你吗
Is that you?!
好吧
Okay.
哈哈 很有意思
Ha ha, very funny.
怎么回事
What the hell?
迪恩
Dean?
怎么
Yeah?
这东西在响
This thing's humming.
等下
Wait.
那个你在实验室调戏的解剖假人
That anatomy dummy you were molesting at the lab.
什么
Excuse me?
也许就是因为这个
What if that's what this is about?
你到底在指控我什么
What exactly are you accusing me of?
我不是那意思
I don't mean that.
那里有个解剖假人
I mean, there was an anatomy dummy there,
而这里
and here…
你开玩笑呢
You're joking.
你没开玩笑
You're not joking.
那么 我们面对的
Okay, uh, so, what, We've got…
我们面对的是一大帮杀人玩偶
we've got a bunch of killer dolls.
就像 查奇（《鬼娃回魂》的主角）
like…Chucky?
不是吧 这简直
I mean, come on, that's … that's just…
太他妈毛骨悚然了
…friggin' creepy.
如果鬼魂能附身人类
I mean, if ghosts can possess humans.
移动物体 为什么他们不能附身这个
and … and move objects, why can't they possess this?
大概吧
I suppose.
给我解释一下 蝙蝠侠
But riddle me this, bat boy …
鬼魂一般不会跨省作案 对吧
Ghosts aren't exactly known for hopping county lines, right?
是的
True.
这家伙袭击了一所学校
This one hits up a college.
现在又是一个工厂 要跨三个城镇
and now a factory, what, three towns over?
不合常理
Doesn't add up.
所以要查啊
So we dig.
在那边
Over there.
我不喜欢金·凯特罗尔（《欲望都市》的女主角）看我的样子
I don't like the way Kim Cattrall's lookin' at me.
这家伙和上一个死者一样背景干净
Well, this dead guy's as squeaky clean as the last dead guy.
我找不到任何污点 你呢
I can't find a speck of dirt on him. You?
什么也没有
Nothing.
找到了
Well, here's a speck.
女裁缝萝丝·布朗一年前失踪了
Uh, seamstress named Rose Brown went missing over a year ago.
警察已经放弃搜寻工作
Uh, cops just gave up on her.
最后一次出现是在工厂 推测已死亡
Last seen at the factory, presumed dead.
妹妹伊莎贝尔尚存
Survived by sister Isabel.
赌50美元 鬼魂复仇
50 bucks … vengeful spirit.
去拜访一下妹妹
Pay sis a visit?
好的
All right.
接吧
Answer it.
莉莎
Lisa?
终于
Finally.
我打了好多次了
I've been calling.
本
Ben?
- 你干嘛… - 妈妈有些不对劲
- What are you - Something's wrong with mom.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
- 很糟 迪恩 - 怎么个糟法
- It's bad, Dean. - Define "bad."
我不知道 她不和我说话
I-I don't know. S-she won't talk to me.
- 好吧 让她接电话 - 她不会接电话的
- All right, put her on the phone. - She won't come to the phone.
本 把电话拿给你妈妈
Ben, get your mom and put her on the phone.
我做不到 她把门锁了
I-I-I can't. Her door's locked.
她基本不下床
She barely gets out of bed.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
求你 来帮帮我
Please just … just come help me.
我不知道怎么办
I-I don't know what to do.
好的 我等下给你打电话
All right, let me call you back.
- 迪恩 - 五分钟后
- Dean - Five minutes.
老弟 我不能就这么离开
Come on, man, I-I can't just leave.
你必须走
Dude, you got to leave.
但是这里事关生死
Yeah, but we're talking life or death here.
好吧 我能撑24小时 迪恩
Right. I can handle it for 24 hours, Dean.
我知道你不想面对这件事
I get you want to bury it.
但是我得处理我的旧事 你也一样
But I had to deal with my past year. You got to deal with yours.
是啊 你处理的可真好
Oh, yeah, and that worked so great for you.
去吧
Come on.
你和萝丝很亲近吧
So, you and Rose were close, huh?
非常
Very.
我们很小的时候父母就去世了
Our parents died when we were little,
我们互相依靠
so we had each other.
她是个什么样的人
What was she like?
善良
Um, kind…
大方
giving.
她有颗宽大的心
She had the biggest heart.
但是有人总是为难她
But people gave her a hard time.
为什么
How come?
她很羞涩 有点笨拙
She was shy, a little awkward.
这让她成为容易被欺负的对象
I guess that made her an easy target.
好像我这一生都在保护她
I feel like I've been defending her my whole life.
她一定很感激
I'm sure she appreciated it.
这是互相的
Well, it went both ways.
她也为我付出了非常多
She did more for me than anybody else ever could.
我很想她
I just miss her.
我能不能看看
Um, may I?
可以 请便
Sure. Please.
这是公司几年前的圣诞派对
Oh, it's a company Christmas party a couple years back.
你也在萨尔兹曼世家工作
Wait, you work at Salzman & Sons, too?
每个人都在工厂干活
Well, everybody works at the factory.
这个是萝丝
That's Rose.
迪恩 听着
Dean, hey, get this.
那个大学看门人
That college janitor?
直到去年 他也一直在那个工厂工作
He worked at the factory, too, until last year.
很显然 萝丝一失踪他就辞职了
Apparently, he quit right after Rose's disappearance.
现在看来 那女孩在工厂肯定出过什么事
So fair bet something happened to that girl around that factory,
所以那里就是整件事的起因
so let's call that joint ground zero.
好吧 但仍然解释不了
Right, but it still doesn't explain.
鬼魂怎么会出现在另一个地区的大学里
how a ghost ended up at a college in another zip code.
这可不像跨界似的
It's not like she hopped the blue line.
我现在去那个工厂
I'm headed to the factory now.
我一查清萝丝的事就打给你
I'll call when I get the whole scoop on Rose.
你来公司多久了
So, how long have you been here with the company?
我在这里大约3年了
I've been here about three years now.
不好意思 这和我有什么关系
I'm sorry, w-what's this got to do with me?
放松点 只是例常询问
Relax. Just a routine questioning.
好的
Oh. Okay.
你认识萝丝·布朗吗
Uh, did you know Rose Brown?
呃
Uh…
也许吧
Maybe.
名字有点耳熟
Uh, the name sounds kind of familiar.
她之前在这儿当裁缝
She was a seamstress here.
一年前失踪了
She went missing about a year ago.
这个
Here.
可以看下吗
You mind taking a look?
是的 我见过她
Uh, yeah, I s… I saw her around.
你能提供些关于她的有用信息吗
Anything you can tell me about her that might help?
听着 我也想帮你
look, I'd love to help,
但我啥也不知道
but I don't know anything.
休息时间结束了 我要迟到了 所以…
And, uh, I'm about to be late back from break, so …
你看起来挺紧张 强尼
You seem nervous, Jonny.
那个
Well.
死去的都是我的朋友
Those guys that died were my friends.
我当然伤心了
O-of course I'm gonna be upset.
我说的不是伤心 而是紧张
I didn't say upset. I said nervous.
给
Here.
想起什么就联系我
In case you remember anything.
迪恩 你来这儿做什么
Dean, what are you doing here?
你看起来很好啊
Well, you look absolutely fine.
怎么回事
What's going on?
是孩子想撮合咱俩
We've been "Parent trapped."
啥
What?
本告诉我情况紧急
Ben sent out a 911.
他为什么要这么做
Why would he do that?
你要去约会 是吧
You're going on a date, huh?
进来吧
Come in.
你想坐下来吗
You want to sit down?
不是很想
Not so much.
那么 那个男人是谁
So, who's the guy?
那个男人是谁
"Who's the guy?"
他叫马特
His name is Matt.
是个医生
He's a doctor.
马特医生
Oh, Dr. Matt.
多体面啊
How respectable.
真的吗 就这样吗
Really? That's how this is gonna be?
听着
Look, I-I …
我给你打过6次电话 迪恩
I called you six times, Dean.
我给你回过近百次电话了
And I almost called you back about 100.
我真欣慰
Good to know.
莉莎 本一打给我
Lis, Ben called me.
我就放下手头的一切赶来了
I dropped everything and ran.
要是你想知道我是不是在乎
If you want to know if I care …
对我无济于事
Doesn't help me.
你想让我怎么着
What do you want from me?
我没有任何要求
I'm not asking for anything.
那就说点要求
Well, then ask for something!
嗯
Um…
- 回你的房间去 - 回你的房间去
- Go to your room! - Go to your room!
你知道 我不能
You know, I…I can't.
对你提要求
Ask for something.
我知道自己想要什么
I know what I want.
但以你的生活方式
But I can't have it …
我无法得到我想要的
not how you live.
我手机一响 我想极小可能是你打来的
My phone rings, I think … tiny chance it's you,
更有可能是萨姆打给我说你死了
big chance it's Sam calling to tell me you're dead.
- 莉莎 - 别 别
- Lis… - No, don't.
别说对不起
Don't apologize or anything.
只是
It's just…
每当我在这里的生活走上正轨
It's just I get to this place where I'm okay,
你就出现在我们家门口
and then you show up at our door.
你总是这样
You keep doing that,
每次在我以为再也见不到你的时候
every time I think I'm never gonna see you again.
我在试着忘却你
I'm trying to get over you.
你又在做什么
What are you trying to do?
你想从我们这里得到什么 迪恩
What do you want from us, Dean?
为什么我快疯了
Why am I flipping out?!
我不知道 也许是因为那些联邦探员
I-I don't know, maybe 'cause of the feds!
因为戴夫和史蒂夫他妈的死了
Maybe 'cause Dave and Steve are freaking dead.
听着 不 不
Look … no. No.
等会再给我电话
Just…Call me later.
快走
Come on.
怎么回事
What's going on?
因为你是个混蛋 所以那个鬼想杀了你
That was a ghost trying to kill you for being a dick.
啥
What?
你知道吗
You know what?
你很幸运 所有被问话的人里面
You're lucky you are the most suspicious interview.
你是最可疑的
of all time.
我就料到会这样
I figured something like this would happen.
料到会怎样
Figured something like what would happen?
伙计 我没时间和你详细解释
Buddy, look, I don't have time for the big speech, all right?
基本事实是
So, brass tacks …
萝丝回来了
Rose is back.
太扯淡了
That's crazy!
你会像你的朋友们一样挂掉
Look, you're gonna end up like your friends.
除非你告诉我你对萝丝做过什么
unless you tell me what you did to Rose.
你想不想让我帮你
Do you want me to help you or not?
那只是个愚蠢的玩笑
It was just a stupid joke.
我是说 人人都会开玩笑
You know, I mean, you … you … you play jokes.
我们没想到会那么严重
We didn't think it was that big of a deal.
你们做了什么
What did you do?
我们让萝丝以为有人暗恋她
We made Rose think she had a secret admirer.
我想那姑娘一辈子都没被人约出去过
I don't think the girl had ever been asked out in her life.
真的 我们只是觉得她有点悲催
Honestly, we just thought she was kind of pathetic…
所以我们知道她会上钩
…So we knew she'd take the bait.
她很兴奋
She was so excited.
那可怜的姑娘压根没想到
The poor girl never saw it coming.
萝丝 我觉得他喜欢你哎
look, Rose, I think he likes you.
那确实很贱
It was mean.
但你知道一帮男人凑一起
But you know how it is when a group of guys get together.
就爱比着谁更混蛋
They … they act like jackasses.
哟 别这样嘛
Aw, don't be like that.
拜托 萝丝 开个玩笑嘛
Come on, Rosey, it's just a joke!
去死吧
Go to hell.
发生得太快了
It happened so fast…
喂 别这么不识逗嘛 萝丝
Hey, take a joke, Rosey.
说真的
Seriously.
我们不是故意的
We didn't mean for it to happen.
但太迟了
And then it was too late.
- 你要干嘛 - 报警啊
- What are you doing? - I'm calling the cops.
- 你疯了吗 - 这是个意外
- Are you crazy? - It was an accident.
是咱骗她来的 我还拽了她
We tricked her here. I grabbed her.
最轻算是过失杀人
That's involuntary manslaughter at least,
前提还得是他们相信咱们
and that's if they even believe us.
你明白吗
You understand?
史蒂夫说我们当时没得选
Steve said there was only one option.
我真希望能重新来过
I wish I could take it all back.
我想你也是
I'm sure you do.
我没杀她
I didn't kill her.
好吧
Okay.
看着我的眼睛
Look me in the eyes.
告诉我一切与你无关
and tell me none of it's on you.
我没说你该死
Look, I'm not saying you deserve to die.
我能帮助你
I can help you.
怎么帮
How?
告诉我你们在哪儿埋的她
You have to tell me where she's buried.
在林子里
In the woods,
峡谷路边的一块空地
a clearing off canyon run road.
- 不 不 你哪儿也别去 - 但我
- No, no, no, no. You're not going anywhere. - But I …
我告诉你没事了之前
You need to stay inside.
你乖乖待在盐线里面
the salt line until I tell you you're safe.
你要让我整宿待在这儿吗
You just want me to stand here all night?!
这已经算不错的了
Consider it getting off easy.
靠 太扯淡了吧
Well, that's ridiculous.
植物才杀不死僵尸
Plants could never kill a zombie.
你觉得我会道歉吗
You think I'm gonna say "I'm sorry"?
为啥我想要你道歉
And why would I think that?
因为你把我骗到这儿来吗
Because you lied to get me here?
紧急情况嘛
It was an emergency.
你妈约个会不叫紧急情况
A date's not an emergency, Ben.
都第三次了还不叫紧急吗
It is if it's the third one.
我看电视的 我知道那是什么意思
I watch TV. I know what that means.
你妈妈是个大人
Well, your mom's a grown-up.
她该出去约会的
She gets to go out.
你为什么不回家
Why won't you come home?
你就不能道个歉 然后回来吗
Can't you just say "I'm sorry" and then come back?
对不起 不行
I'm sorry. I can't.
是不行还是不愿意
Can't or won't?
都有
Both.
- 那你现在就是恨我妈了 - 啥 当然不是
- So, you hate mom now? - What? No, come on.
- 那就是因为我了呗 - 本 别瞎想了
- So it's me. - Ben, stop it.
不管我怎么你了 我道歉还不行吗
Whatever I did, I'm sorry.
听我说
Listen to me.
你什么也没做
You didn't do anything.
你明白吗
You understand that?
听好 总有一天 你会…
Look, one day you'll, uh…
你长大了就明白了
You'll get this when you're older.
别拿我当小孩子
Don't talk to me like I'm six.
得
Okay, fine.
那我就这么说吧
It's like this, then.
你爱某个人 那并不意味着
Just 'cause you love someone.
就要在他们身边 扰乱他们的生活
doesn't mean you should stick around and screw up their life.
所以我不能回来
So I can't be here.
你觉得会有东西跟着你回来吗
You think something will follow you home?
不 不是的
No, I don't,
但我想由于我的工作
but I think my job turns me into somebody.
让我无法拥有一个家庭
that can't sit at your dinner table.
如果我留下
And if I stayed,
会让你变得跟我一样
you'd end up just like me.
你为什么把自己说得那么…坏
Why do you say it like you're so…bad?
相信我 我可绝不是你的榜样
Well, trust me, I'm not someone you want to aim to be.
- 不能听听我的意见吗 - 不能
- Don't I get a vote? - No, you don't.
对不起 本
I'm sorry, Ben.
但是 这样你才能有机会
But, see, this way you got a shot.
实现自己想要的人生
at living whatever life you want.
你知道的 可以有的选
You know, pick one.
选五种都可以
Pick five.
因为和我在一起 只有这一条道走到黑
'cause with me, there's just the one road.
- 你骗人 迪恩 - 啥
- You're a liar, Dean. - Excuse me?
你说家人大过天
You say family's so important,
但是 无论你多混蛋 都还是关心你
but … but what do you call people who … who care for you,
爱你的人 你当他们是什么
who love you even when you're a dick?
你知道你这是在抛弃家人 对吗
You know you're walking out on your family, right?
好了 解决了 你安全了
All right, it's over. You're safe.
强尼
And, Jonny?
把这次当做新的开始吧
Look at this as a new beginning.
想不当混蛋 机会多得是
Lot of chances not to be a jackass.
（麦克欧文酒吧）
珍妮
Jenny?
宝 咱要走了
Hon…We're leaving…
今晚就走
Tonight.
收拾一下吧 带些必需品就好
So, pack up. Just the essentials.
我只想继续过我们的生活
All I want is for us to move on with our lives.
我爱你
I love you.
你知道的
You know that.
一直…
It's been…
一直都很难 珍
It's been really hard, Jen.
这是迪恩的二号替补电话
This is Dean's other other cell,
你知道怎么做的
so you must know what to do.
喂 那事没结束
Hey, it's not over.
烧掉尸体没能阻止她
Burning the remains didn't stop her.
她一定是跟别的什么还有关联
She's got to be hooked to something else.
我现在要去找她妹 回我
I'm gonna head to the sister's now. Call me.
就这些了吗
So, um, this is it?
多数她的衣服我都捐出去了
I gave most of her clothes to the goodwill.
不过她也没多少
She didn't have much.
那些是你的吗
Those yours?
是的
Yeah.
你还在上学吗
Are you in school?
- 哪所学校 - 大瀑布
- Where? - Uh, Great Falls.
容我猜一下
So let me guess…
这周你去过化学实验室和工厂
Um, you were at the chem lab and the factory this week.
是的
Well, yeah.
你昨晚有没有去过一家叫麦克欧文的酒吧
Did you happen to stop by a bar called Mcowen's last night?
工厂里的人都去那里
Everybody from the factory goes there.
我大概一周去三次
I stop in maybe three times a week.
怎么了
Why?
这就对了
That's it.
- 这都是你的缘故 - 什么啊
- So this is all about you. - What? What is?
那些凶杀案 你的同事们
The murders … your coworkers,
你的大学看门人
your college janitor.
什么啊 你认为是我干的
What, you … you think I could do something like that?!
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
不过 我觉得你是整件事的关键
But … but I think you're at the center.
我 怎么说
Me? How?
你戴了萝丝的什么东西 戒指 手镯
What are you wearing of Rose's? A ring? A bracelet?
- 她的乳牙吊坠 是什么 - 你吓到我了
- Her baby teeth in a locket? What? - You're scaring me.
你想想 拜托
Just think, please.
你身上有什么东西
What … what do you have.
- 是萝丝的 - 我…
- of Rose that you carry with you? - I-I'm…
是什么
What?
我的身体里面有一样她的东西
Well, the only thing I have of hers is a part of me.
我十六岁的时候
When I was 16,
她把她的一个肾捐给了我
she gave me one of her kidneys.
她的肾
Her kidney?
对
Yeah.
开玩笑的吧
You're kidding.
你能不能告诉我这到底是怎么回事
Will you please tell me what this is about?
可以
Yeah. Um…
但是你得跟我走一趟
But I'm gonna need you to come with me.
就是那女孩体内有「鬼肾」吗
So, that the girl with the haunted kidney?
对
Yeah.
真是大开眼界了
Well, just when you think you seen it all.
你想怎么做
What do you want to do?
不能直接烧了它啊
Can't exactly burn the thing.
她需要这个肾
I mean, she kind of needs it.
她不能带着它到处走啊 迪恩
Well, she can't just walk around with it, Dean.
鬼魂和肾脏相联
The spirit's attached.
它会利用她来找到它想报复的人
It's gonna use her to get close to anyone it wants revenge on.
它不会停止杀戮
It's not gonna stop killing.
那你什么意思 把肾从她身体里取出来吗
Okay, so what are you suggesting, that we cut it out of her?
然后呢
And then what?
把她放在装满冰的浴缸里
Leave her in a tub of ice.
绑个电话在她手上
with a phone taped to her hand?
我们可以打电话给罗伯特医生
Maybe we should call Dr. Robert.
他可能知道黑市上有没有
Might have some leads on some.
正常的可替换的肾脏
non-haunted, black-market replacement kidneys.
他在一家肉店工作
He works out of a butcher shop.
那里很干净 你肯定会大吃一惊
It's pretty clean. You'd be surprised.
不 我觉得我们得靠巫术了
No. I think we have to go Hoodoo.
- 巫术 - 对
- Hoodoo? - Yeah, Hoodoo.
那最多是权宜之计 治标不治本啊
That's more of a band-aid, not really a cure.
至少能争取些时间
It buys us a minute.
好吧 那就去路易斯安那州
All right, Louisiana it is.
「伏都」
Voodoo?!
你们在瞎掰什么啊
What the hell are you talking about?
事实上应该叫巫术
Actually, it's "hoodoo."
有点儿差别
It's a little different.
- 打住 伊莎贝尔 - 你们不是联调局的人
- Hold on, Isabel. - You're not feds.
请容我们解释
Just let us explain.
不是吧
No.
坑爹啊
No way.
这不可能
That's impossible.
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
她附身性爱娃娃 这又不是性爱娃娃
She possesses sex dolls! This … this is not a sex doll!
别碰我的宝贝儿
Hey, you leave my baby alone!
跟她没关系
She's got nothing to do with this!
跑 跑 跑啊
go, go, go, go, go!
这里 这里 进去
Okay, here, here, here. Get in.
你个狗杂种
Son of a bitch!
宝贝儿 对不起了
I'm so sorry, baby.
好了
Okay.
你没事吧
You all right?
没事没事 我很好 你们呢
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good. You guys?
没事
Yeah.
对 我…
Yeah, I'm…
伊莎贝尔
Isabel?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我本意绝非如此
I didn't mean for this.
怎么样了
How's it look?
考虑到她被鬼劫持
Well, considering she got carjacked by poltergeist,
不幸中的万幸了
could be worse.
萨姆 我们到底做了什么啊
I mean, what exactly did we do back there, Sam?
对啊 赢得太不光荣
Yeah, I'm not putting it in the win column, either.
我们救了几个混蛋
We saved a few dicks,
但是杀了一个无辜的女孩
a-a-and we killed an innocent girl.
我让我的孩子伤心
I got a heartbroken kid.
还令我的女人生气
and a woman who's so pissed at me…
我算明白你说面对过去是什么意思了
I see what you mean about facing your past.
那…
It's, uh.
- 真是超赞 谢谢 - 迪恩
- it's awesome. Thanks. - Dean.
我们只会把事情搞得乱七八糟
I mean, all we do is make a mess.
不是的
That's not true.
我们偶尔还拯救生命
We do save lives, now and again.
对 没错
Yeah, I guess.
我只是…
I'm just…
幸运女神老是不眷顾我们 我很郁闷
I'm just tired of all the bad luck, you know?
你要知道 第一
Well, you know, number one,
猎魔这工作也就意味着走霉运
bad luck is kind of in the job description.
第二 也不全是倒霉事儿
And two, it's not all bad.
真的 看看我
Really. Look at me.
至少 撒旦已经不在了
I mean, at least Satan's left the building.
对
Yeah.
这倒是不错
It's the little things.
因为你 我又有灵魂了
And I have a soul because of you.
我还没谢过你 对吧
I never thanked you for that, did I?
不用客气 老弟
Ah, it's all good, man.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
换做是你 你也会这么做
You'd have done the same for me.
我真心的
I mean it.
我们保持低调 继续前行
Look, we keep our heads down, keep swinging.
当然有失 但是希望能得到更多
We'll lose some. Hopefully, we'll win more.
还有
And…
我不知道
I don't know.
不论如何 反正
Anyway, for what it's worth,
有我罩你
I got your back.
我知道
Yeah, I know.